{
  "1": [
    {
      "question": "If I _____ near the sea, I would sunbathe every day .",
      "correctAnswer": "lived",
      "incorrectAnswers": "live"
    },
    {
      "question": "If we _____ a million, we would help the poor .",
      "correctAnswer": "had",
      "incorrectAnswers": "have"
    },
    {
      "question": "If he _____ English, he would find a good job .",
      "correctAnswer": "knew",
      "incorrectAnswers": "knows"
    },
    {
      "question": "If I _____ very rich, I would buy what I want .",
      "correctAnswer": "was",
      "incorrectAnswers": "am"
    },
    {
      "question": "If he _____ strong, he would lift this box .",
      "correctAnswer": "was",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is"
    },
    {
      "question": "If she was here, she _____ us .",
      "correctAnswer": "would help",
      "incorrectAnswers": "will help"
    },
    {
      "question": "If she was in the shop now, she _____ you some sweets .",
      "correctAnswer": "would buy",
      "incorrectAnswers": "will buy"
    },
    {
      "question": "If I were you, I _____ my hair .",
      "correctAnswer": "would comb",
      "incorrectAnswers": "will comb"
    },
    {
      "question": "If I were him, I _____ the truth .",
      "correctAnswer": "would tell",
      "incorrectAnswers": "will tell"
    },
    {
      "question": "If it rained, you _____ wet .",
      "correctAnswer": "would get",
      "incorrectAnswers": "will get"
    },
    {
      "question": "You _____ so tired if you went to bed earlier .",
      "correctAnswer": "wouldn't be",
      "incorrectAnswers": "won't be"
    },
    {
      "question": "She _____ herself if she fell .",
      "correctAnswer": "would hurt",
      "incorrectAnswers": "will hurt"
    },
    {
      "question": "We _____ to the park if the weather wasn't so bad .",
      "correctAnswer": "would go",
      "incorrectAnswers": "will go"
    },
    {
      "question": "I _____ and see her if I knew where she lived .",
      "correctAnswer": "would go",
      "incorrectAnswers": "will go"
    },
    {
      "question": "I _____ this dress if I were taller .",
      "correctAnswer": "would buy",
      "incorrectAnswers": "will buy"
    },
    {
      "question": "I would travel the world if I _____ 20 .",
      "correctAnswer": "was",
      "incorrectAnswers": "am"
    },
    {
      "question": "I would be very happy if I _____ a good job .",
      "correctAnswer": "had",
      "incorrectAnswers": "have"
    },
    {
      "question": "He would buy a car if he _____ the lottery .",
      "correctAnswer": "won",
      "incorrectAnswers": "wins"
    },
    {
      "question": "They would call you if they _____ a phone .",
      "correctAnswer": "had",
      "incorrectAnswers": "have"
    },
    {
      "question": "She would cook dinner if she _____ enough time .",
      "correctAnswer": "had",
      "incorrectAnswers": "has"
    }
  ],
  "2": [
    {
      "question": "If I _____ # near the sea, I would sunbathe every day .",
      "correctAnswer": "lived",
      "incorrectAnswers": "live"
    },
    {
      "question": "If we _____ # a million, we would help the poor .",
      "correctAnswer": "had",
      "incorrectAnswers": "have"
    },
    {
      "question": "If he _____ # English, he would find a good job .",
      "correctAnswer": "knew",
      "incorrectAnswers": "knows"
    },
    {
      "question": "If I _____ # very rich, I would buy what I want .",
      "correctAnswer": "was",
      "incorrectAnswers": "am"
    },
    {
      "question": "If he _____ # strong, he would lift this box .",
      "correctAnswer": "was",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is"
    },
    {
      "question": "If she was here, she _____ # us .",
      "correctAnswer": "would help",
      "incorrectAnswers": "will help"
    },
    {
      "question": "If she was in the shop now, she _____ # you some sweets .",
      "correctAnswer": "would buy",
      "incorrectAnswers": "will buy"
    },
    {
      "question": "If I were you, I _____ # my hair .",
      "correctAnswer": "would comb",
      "incorrectAnswers": "will comb"
    },
    {
      "question": "If I were him, I _____ # the truth .",
      "correctAnswer": "would tell",
      "incorrectAnswers": "will tell"
    },
    {
      "question": "If it rained, you _____ # wet .",
      "correctAnswer": "would get",
      "incorrectAnswers": "will get"
    },
    {
      "question": "You _____ # so tired if you went to bed earlier .",
      "correctAnswer": "wouldn't be",
      "incorrectAnswers": "won't be"
    },
    {
      "question": "She _____ # herself if she fell .",
      "correctAnswer": "would hurt",
      "incorrectAnswers": "will hurt"
    },
    {
      "question": "We _____ # to the park if the weather wasn't so bad .",
      "correctAnswer": "would go",
      "incorrectAnswers": "will go"
    },
    {
      "question": "I _____ # and see her if I knew where she lived .",
      "correctAnswer": "would go",
      "incorrectAnswers": "will go"
    },
    {
      "question": "I _____ # this dress if I were taller .",
      "correctAnswer": "would buy",
      "incorrectAnswers": "will buy"
    },
    {
      "question": "I would travel the world if I _____ # 20 .",
      "correctAnswer": "was",
      "incorrectAnswers": "am"
    },
    {
      "question": "I would be very happy if I _____ # a good job .",
      "correctAnswer": "had",
      "incorrectAnswers": "have"
    },
    {
      "question": "He would buy a car if he _____ # the lottery .",
      "correctAnswer": "won",
      "incorrectAnswers": "wins"
    },
    {
      "question": "They would call you if they _____ # a phone .",
      "correctAnswer": "had",
      "incorrectAnswers": "have"
    },
    {
      "question": "She would cook dinner if she _____ # enough time .",
      "correctAnswer": "had",
      "incorrectAnswers": "has"
    }
  ]
}